My new camera.
Try adjusting the settings.
The lighting is good here.
Where are we going?
This place is quite hard to find.
What's wrong?
This client is a Taiwanese compatriot
named Lin Siyuan.
His grandfather
is from Shishan, Nan'an.
His grandfather settled in Taiwan over 40 years ago.
He always talks about his hometown's Shishan Powan.
So he came back this time
to find the taste from his grandfather's memory.
But this shop is really hard to find.
I've been looking for it for a long time.
Some people online even say
it moved away a long time ago.
It's over in the Ximei Old Town area.
Let me see.
Why do I keep feeling
like someone is watching me from behind?
What's wrong?
Where is Xinyue?
She said she was checking out the route
to help the client from Taiwan
find the taste of home.
You didn't drive?
Someone is driving for her.
I'm happy to relax.
Who? A newbie?
Just a guy.
With his styled hair and hairspray.
By the way, he said he's your landlord.
Really?
Yeah, that whole building is his.
What, are you jealous?
Or do you like Li Xinyue?
Sir.
Do you know this place?
I remember.
Huang's Powan in Shishan old market.
But due to the old town renovation,
the businesses there all moved away.
Do you know where they moved?
It seems they were all relocated to
the new market on the south bank of Xixi.
But that was decades ago.
Who knows where they moved to.
Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
Let's go.
I
like her.
I couldn't tell you guys were so humorous.
If you don't like him, why are you jealous?
Jealous?
How could I be jealous?
This is the anger of a shareholder
who has been deprived of decision-making power.
But we haven't even said who it is.
I said it, okay?
I'm talking about them.
Okay.
When do you think they'll be back?
What does it have to do with me?
They can come back whenever they want.
I just checked the weather forecast.
It looks like it's going to rain heavily.
It's going to rain heavily.
Again, what does it have to do with me?
Let it rain.
Yiyi, tell me.
The roads are slippery in the rain.
What if the car breaks down?
What if the road is bad
and the car is hard to drive?
It's hard to drive.
It's not like you're driving a convertible.
I thought you took the bag out to block the rain.
This bag is very expensive, okay, young master?
If the bag gets ruined by the rain, you can buy a new one.
If you get sick from the rain, you'll need medicine, injections, and hospitalization.
Look at you.
Stop, stop, stop.
Can't you wish me well?
No.
I'm not saying you're going to immediately
need medicine, injections, and hospitalization.
Hey,
Li Xinyue.
Who is it?
A helpful citizen.
We Nan'an people are quite enthusiastic.
Thank you.
Let me hold the umbrella.
No.
The rain is still heavy.
Let's wait a while.
Wait until it gets lighter.
Just get closer to me.
Li Xinyue, are you an idiot?
Who is this again?
Hardship only flows to those who can endure it.
Zhang Yang, Zhang Yang.
Hardship only flows to you who can endure it.
Why are you still dawdling?
Hurry up and come out with me to find a shop.
What's wrong?
Speak.
Xinyue,
I came back in the heavy rain yesterday and got a high fever.
Now everything I eat is tasteless.
My throat and head are burning with pain.
This is what Mr. Zhang wants to say to you.
Right, Mr. Zhang?
I can understand the rest.
But how did you tell it's 'hot'?
It's just a feeling.
Come on, Zhang Yang.
Show me the gesture again.
Well,
he went to pick you up in the heavy rain yesterday.
He fell on his way back
and scraped his knee.
Maybe we should let him rest today.
So you're really not faking it.
Let me see where you're hurt.
Alright.
You stay home today.
I'll go find Qin Fei.
Don't.
Qin Fei went out to carry bags for Mr. Tang today.
Maybe I should still go with you.
But you have to take good care of me.
I'll go by myself.
You stay home and recover.
Don't.
Well, if I go
with you today, can I still get my meals reimbursed?
I can't if I stay here.
I'll reimburse your meals.
Remember to get the receipt.
Um, can I buy some sea cucumbers and abalones to nourish myself?
Oh, right.
And caviar,
and Angus steak.
Do you want to eat your sick meals at a Black Pearl restaurant?
You two.
Singing the same tune.
Did you rehearse this?
Okay.
Hurry up.
I'll take you out.
Why are you dawdling?
Are you waiting for me to carry you down?
Hurry up.
Let's take a picture here later.
What's wrong?
What is this?
I know it's a ring.
Beg me.
Say please.
What exactly do you want to say?
Why is your face so red?
You still have a fever.
Let me take your temperature.
You do it yourself.
You don't have a fever.
It's quite serious, isn't it?
Maybe this isn't accurate.
I'll take you to the hospital to take your rectal temperature.
No.
Such a loud voice.
It doesn't seem inflamed.
Let's drop it and get to work.
Let's hurry up and go.